Finding Aid for the Ronnie Steinberg Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Ronnie Steinberg Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0942
13.75 linear_feet
- Letter of Nomination of me to Tennessee Council on Econ. Status of Women (Box 1)
- W-SPARC Planning (Box 1)
- Three-Pager (Box 1)
- Strategic Plan (Box 1)
- Population Statistics (Box 1)
- Disenrollment Info www.tennessee.gov/tenncare (Box 1)
- Affirmative Action/Diversity Award (Box 1)
- Unlabeled (Box 1)
- IWPR 2005 Presentation (Box 1)
- Economic Summit for Women 2004 Presentation (Box 1)
- Scholarship Directory Presentation Materials (Box 1)
- Directory Proposal Project Presentations (Box 1)
- Unlabeled (Box 1)
- Tennessean Articles (Box 1)
- TN Journal (Box 1)
- Unlabeled (Box 1)
- Unlabeled (Box 1)
- Living Wage (Box 1)
- Living Wage Packets (Box 1)
- PACE-Fact Sheets (Box 2)
- Subverting Organizational Containment: Sexual Harassment/Sexual Assult 7/94 Final Draft (Box 2)
- Sexual harassment/Sexual Assault Policy-Summer Money 1995 Proposal (Box 2)
- ESS Abstract-Subverting Org Containment (Box 2)
- Subverting Organizational Containment: Maxim. The Scope of S.H.S.A. Policies + Programs (Box 2)
- Sex. Harassment Paper-Italy (Box 2)
- Talks/papers for Talk prep-2001-2002 Athena Speech-Fierce Advocacy for the 21st Century (Box 2)
- TECW-Post-Vern Memos (Box 2)
- TECW-Goals-Objectives (Box 2)
- TECW Mission + Vision (Box 2)
- Tennessee Economic Council on Women Statute Highlights (Box 2)
- TECW-Bylaws (Box 2)
- TECW-Brochure (Box 2)
- State of Tennessee Biennial Report TECW - Sept. 1, 2000 (Box 2)
- IWPR State Reports - Research - in - Brief Summaries (Box 2)
- Status of Women in Tennessee - News Clippings release of report (Box 2)
- Nashville Business Journal article on Statis of Women in Tennessee (Box 2)
- Vanderbilt Register Article on SWTN report (Box 2)
- Fact Book: preface (Box 2)
- Focus Box: Race + Educational Attainment (Box 2)
- Focus Box: Income Householder by Race (Box 2)
- Focus Box on the Gender Gap Fact Book (Box 2)
- Gender Gap Statistics for Tennessee Voter News Service (Box 2)
- Focus Box: IWPR- Dist. Of Wages by Female Dom/ Male Dominated/ Gender-Neutral Jobs- Alloccs, services (Box 2)
- Domestic Violence Data for IWPR report (Box 2)
- The Welfare to Work Challenge for Adult Literacy Educators (Box 2)
- National-federal LF data from Martha Wettermann (Box 2)
- State Living Wage Data: %F merge w/ Occ Wage Data (Box 2)
- Press Conference Remarks: Press kit May 10, 2000 (Box 2)
- Letters to the Editor - Tennessean Equal Pay Rebuttal (Box 2)
- Equal Pay Day: Press Conference - May 10, 2000 Press Release (Box 2)
- Original Devaney Press Conference Remarks for RS (Box 2)
- Press Conference - may 10, 2000 National Equal Pay Day - Remarks of Ronnie Steinberg (Box 2)
- Post-Press Conference news clippikngs + update - May 15, 2000 (Box 2)
- Equal Pay Law: Tennessee 5/9/2000 (Box 2)
- IWPR - Status of Women Report - Focus Boxes (Box 2)
- National + State Data on the Pay Gap + Its Costs - AFL - CIO (Box 2)
- TECW - Listening Tour Report (Box 2)
- W-SPARC + Survey on Domestic Violence Nat'l Coalition Against Domestic Violence (Box 2)
- Handouts: Tax Study: Chart (Box 2)
- Jennifer Karpinski: Tax Return Paper (Box 2)
- Impact on Tax Reform on Tennessee Women Memo (Box 2)
- Tax Impact: Methodology + Proposals (detailed) + assumptions (Box 2)
- 6/4/01: Presentation on Tax Impact Study before Joint Committee-Tennessee Legislature (Box 2)
- Income tax Estimates - 11/01 Flat Tax (Naifeh) + Income Tax (Box 2)
- Economic Independence for Women in Tennessee-Is it possible? -speech- (Box 2)
- Economci Independence for Women in Tennessee. Is it possible - 10/25/01 Women in Medicine (Box 2)
- Econ. Independence for Women in Tennessee Overheads (Box 2)
- Handouts: Living Wage Calculations (Box 2)
- Living Wage Paper-Charts (Box 2)
- W-SPARC-Praise (Box 2)
- Nashville Living Wage Campaign 5/15/01 Speech for Rally (Box 2)
- Living Wage: Estimates of Costs re: Metro Contacts (Box 2)
- Living Wage: Testimony RS: draft (Box 2)
- CPS Data-Distribut of Income by family Nashville (Box 2)
- Input/ouotput Analysis: Living Wage (Box 2)
- Metro Council Living Wage Ordinance - Media (Box 2)
- Spreadsheet: Contract Data Initial data from which computations made (Box 2)
- Bruce Berry: passing the Buck Scene on RS/AP Living Wage Reform + Mercer Study (Box 2)
- Letter to Bill Purcell w/ Bruce Berry (Box 2)
- Living Wage: Pamphlet (Box 2)
- Nashville Living Wage-2001 Clippings (Box 2)
- TECW-News Clippings-General 1989-2000 (Box 2)
- Tennessee Economic Council on Women Cable Luncheon + Media (Box 2)
- Tax Study Bibliography Beverly Moran (Box 2)
- SPARC Accomplishments (Box 3)
- Women + Sporta: Conference Proposal (Box 3)
- Immigrant Women Proposals (Box 3)
- Potential Solicitors (Box 3)
- Tax Impact Study--Spreadsheets (Box 3)
- Consumer Expenditure Survey 1999 (Box 3)
- Nell Levin - paper on businesses + TN Tax Reform (Box 3)
- CPS: Distribut. Of Income by family type for estimates of tax impact (Box 3)
- Tenn. Journal Summary: Sales + use Tax: Current Structure (Box 3)
- Tax Reform Proposals: Summaries (Box 3)
- Current Sales Tax (Box 3)
- Rochelle: Sales Tax Categories (Box 3)
- Sundguest 2001 (Box 3)
- The 2001 Metro Blue Book-Nashville-Davidson County-League of Women Voters (Box 3)
- Budget Impact Report (Box 3)
- SUV-Living Wage-VU (Box 3)
- Jennifer Karpinski: The Impact of Tax Reform on Women (Box 3)
- TEAC Report: Draft (Box 3)
- TEAC Correlations-Employees (Box 3)
- TEAC Results: Tables (Box 3)
- TEAC Study: Results of Warmth Survey (Box 3)
- TEAC-Survey Results (Box 3)
- Unlabeled (Box 3)
- TEAC Facility Proposals-Sample facilities (Box 3)
- Letter to Eden Tn. Board on TEAC study (Box 3)
- Unlabeled (Box 4)
- Unlabeled (Box 4)
- Unlabeled (Box 4)
- Transportation (Box 4)
- Unlabeld (Box 4)
- Unlabeled (Box 4)
- Unlabeled (Box 4)
- 5-Year Plan (Box 4)
- Health Care reports To Get (Box 4)
- Unlabeled (Box 4)
- Tennessee Health Status Reports TN Dept. of Health -'98-'02 (Box 4)
- Unlabeled (Box 4)
- TennCare Changes Effect Aug. 1, 2005 (Box 4)
- Unlabeled (Box 5)
- Unlabeled (Box 5)
- Unlabeled (Box 5)
- Unlabeled (Box 5)
- Christina-Research (Box 5)
- Women on Boards (Box 5)
- Elder Data Not w Report (Box 5)
- Interdisciplinar-Women's Studies Annual Report 1999,2000 (Box 6)
- Riley Lecture-Alfred Univ.: Econ War Against ♀ (Box 6)
- Karen Porter, Intro. To my Riley Lecture Alfred University April 11, 1996 (Box 6)
- Living Wage Campaign Nashville 1999 (Box 6)
- The Impact of Living Wage Ordinance on the Public Contracting Process-Jared Bernstein (Box 6)
- Living Wage Campaign: A Step in the Right Direction EPI - Jared Bernstein (Box 6)
- CROW- Living Wage I Memphis Ciscel (Box 6)
- How Much is Enough? Basic Family Budget for Working Families Jared Bernstein; Chawna Brocht + Maggie Spade-Aquilar (Box 6)
- Domestic Vioolence Report Project Fighting Back With Facts: Getting the Research you need to build a movement (Box 6)
- W-SPARC: Memphis Confscto (Box 6)
- W-SPARC-Development Other Centers' Donor Lists (Box 6)
- Ronnie-Annual Report Info for 2001/2002 (Box 6)
- Tax Structure Study Commission Proposal (Box 6)
- City Council - TennCare (Box 6)
- Unlabeled (Box 6)
- Immigrant Research (Box 6)
- Unlabeled (Box 6)
- Class Record Book (Box 7)
- Notebook with miscellanous notes from interviews, classes, and conferences (Box 7)
- Notebook with miscellanous notes (Box 7)
- Notebook with miscellanous notes (Box 7)
- Notebook with miscellanous notes (Box 7)
- Notebook with miscellanous notes (Box 7)
- Notebook miscellanous notes (Box 7)
- Notebook with miscellanous notes (Box 7)
- Notebook with miscellanous notes (Box 7)
- Conference Notes Spring 1998-Summer 1998 (Notebook) (Box 7)
- Conference Notes Notebook (Box 7)
- VU Speeches + Seminars Notebook (Box 7)
- Notebook with miscellanous notes (Box 7)
- Center Proposal: Clowning (Box 8)
- Ford Grant: Core Funding (Box 8)
- Leadership Proposal (Box 8)
- Reviewed Funding Info Currently Useful (Box 8)
- SFC grants TN (Box 8)
- The Living Wage Campaign Maria Tsagaris (Box 8)
- Living Wage Paper (Box 8)
- Unlabeled (Box 8)
- Living Wage Alisa's Notes/Data (Box 8)
- Fall 2000 + Spring 2001 Schedules Turned in 3-9-00 (Box 8)
- Alisa's Data Cont. (Box 8)
- Cost of Living Info (Box 8)
- LW Articles + Studies (Box 8)
- State Wage Data (Box 8)
- Living Wage Mtg. Minutes (Box 8)
- Living Wage Articles (Box 8)
- Ferret Data (Box 8)
- Living Wage-Mercer (Box 8)
- Unlabeled
- Unlabeled (Box 9)
- TACIR Reports (Box 9)
- Tax Proposal Summaries (Box 9)
- Tax Paper- Final Tax Calculations (Box 9)
- Tax Graphs (Box 9)
- Tax Paper (Box 9)
- Tax Guide-2001 TN (Box 9)
- 2002 Tennessee Tax Guide (Box 9)
- Tax Reform (Box 9)
- Status Quo Sales tax Consumer Bundle, Sunquist '99 TFT (Box 9)
- Who Pays? (Box 9)
- Rochelle Calculations (Box 9)
- Rochelle (Box 9)
- Sundquist 2001 (Box 9)
- Head (Box 9)
- Status Quo Taxes (Box 9)
- Old Sundquist (Box 9)
- Sundquist 2001 (Box 9)
- Unlabeled (Box 9)
- Recent Research April-May 2004, 2004-03/2004-05 (Box 9)
- Meeting Notes (Jen) (Box 9)
- Contacts (Jen) (Box 9)
- CES (Jen) (Box 9)
- Sundquist Proposal 1999 (Jen) (Box 9)
- Sundquist Proposal 2001 (Jen) (Box 9)
- TFT Proposal (Jen) (Box 9)
- Curent Tax System (Jen) (Box 9)
- Rochelle Proposal (Jen) (Box 9)
- TFT (Jen) (Box 9)
- IRS Data (Jen) (Box 9)
- ITEP Studies (Jen) (Box 9)
- Academic Studies on Income Distribution (Jen) (Box 9)
- SEWSA Presentation (Jen) (Box 9)
- DV and Housing (Box 9)
- State Tax 2004-Final Report (Box 9)
- Unlabeled (Box 9)
- Final Report of the Tennessee Tax Structure Study Commission December 2004 (Box 9)
- 2004 Tennessee Tax Guide (Box 9)
- State Tax 2004 Contract (Box 9)
- State Tax (Box 9)
- Tax Structure Study Commission (Box 9)
- CES (Box 9)
- Unlabeled (Box 9)
- To files in WS (Box 9)
- Unlabeled (Box 10)
- Unlabeled (Box 10)
- Unlabeled (Box 10)
- Car Loans (Box 10)
- Unlabeled (Box 10)
- Unlabeled (Box 10)
- Thornton, Michael and Shelley White-Means. 2000. "race versus Ethnic Heritage in Models of Family Economic Decisions." (Box 10)
- Hrung, Warren. 2001. "The Civil Rights Act of 1964 and Black Consumption/Savings Behavior." (Box 10)
- Fan, Jessie and Virginia S. Zuiker. 1998. "A Comparison of Household Budget Allocation Patterns between Hispanic Americans and Non-Hispanic White Americans." (Box 10)
- Kivett, Vira and Frankie Schwenk. 1994. "the Consumer Expenditures of Elderly Women: Racial, Marital, and Rural/Urban Impacts." (Box 10)
- Cohen, Philip. 1998. "Replacing Housework in the Service Economy: Gender, Class, and Race-Ethnicity in Service Spending." (Box 10)
- Circarelli, James. 1974. "On Income, Race, and Consumer Behavior." The American Journal of Economics and Sociology 33(3)." (Box 10)
- Brayfield, April and Sandra Hofferth. 1995. "Balancing the Family Budget: Differences in Child Care Expenditures by Race, Ethnicity, Economic Status, and Family Structure" (Box 10)
- Unlabeled (Box 10)
- Tax Reform Memo (Box 10)
- 501c3 + Tax Exempt Ltr (Box 10)
- AAUW Progress in Equity 2004 (Box 10)
- Allegra FootPRINT fund (Box 10)
- Grant Application-Community FDTN of Middle TN (Box 10)
- FRIST (Box 10)
- MS. (Box 10)
- Ford Foundation (Box 10)
- Grants to look into (Box 10)
- Grants (Box 10)
- Harnisch (Box 10)
- Humanities TN 2005 (Box 10)
- Grant Application Nashville Women's Breakfast Club 2002 (Box 10)
- SLOMAN (Box 10)
- Humanities Tennessee 2004 (Box 10)
- Immigrant ♀ Grant
- Junior League Grant Keystone Grant 2004 (Box 10)
- VU Community Giving (Box 10)
- Faculty Development Grant 2005 Vanderbilt Internal (Box 10)
- Foundation Lists (Box 10)
- Potential Grants (Box 10)
- AETNA (Box 10)
- Annie E. Casey Foundation (Box 10)
- Appalachian Community Fund (Box 10)
- ASTRAEA Foundation (Box 10)
- ATT (Box 10)
- Avon (Box 10)
- Ben + Jerry's (Box 10)
- Carnegie (Box 10)
- Community Foundation of Greater Memphis (Box 10)
- Community Foundation of Middle Tennessee (Box 10)
- Educational Foundation of America (Box 10)
- Fund for Southern Communities (Box 10)
- Funding Exchange (Box 10)
- Global Fund for ♀ (Not Relevant to W-SPARC) (Box 10)
- HCA Foundation (Box 10)
- Hope VI Grants (VIPPS) (Box 10)
- Levi Strauss Foundation (Box 10)
- Macarthur Foundation (Box 10)
- Moriah Fund (Box 10)
- MS Foundation (Box 10)
- The New York Community TRUST (Box 10)
- Open Society Foundation Institute (Box 10)
- David and Lucille Packand FDN (Box 10)
- Ottinger Foundation (Box 10)
- Plough Foudnation (Box 10)
- Public Welfare FDN (Box 10)
- Rockefeller Foundation (Box 10)
- Alfred P. Sloan (Box 10)
- Surdna (Box 10)
- Thre Guineas Fund (Box 10)
- Women's Foundation of Greater Memphis (Box 10)
- Valentine Foundation
- Unlabeled (Box 11)
- Incoming Gifts to process (Box 11)
- Contribution List Reports W-SPARC (Box 11)
- Contribution List Reports Women's Studies (Box 11)
- Process Gifts July 2004-June 2005 (Box 11)
- Processed Gifts (Box 11)
- Donors (Box 11)
- Donor Thank You's (Box 11)
- Door Thank You's -Done- (Box 11)
- Thank You Samples (Box 11)
- Direct Mail Lists (Box 11)
- Newsletter (Box 11)
- Bank Draft (Box 11)
- Fundraising Event (Box 11)
- Tablehosts (Box 11)
- Black Sororities + Banks (Funding Leads) (Box 11)
- Cable List (Box 11)
- Donations (Box 11)
- Fundraising Newsletter- Mal Warwick (Box 11)
- Memphis Info (Box 11)
- Philanthropy Newsletter (Box 11)
- Potential Major Donor (Box 11)
- Fundraising Thousand Sparcs (Box 11)
- WSPARC Fundraising (Box 11)
- Marketing Concept 2002 (Box 11)
- Fundraising (Box 11)
- W-SPARC Fundraising Letter (Box 11)
- Fundraising Info (Box 11)
- Board (Box 11)
- Fundraising Sample (Box 11)
- LK + JH VU front + back (Box 11)
- Membership Examples (Box 11)
- Backpages (X-TRA) (Box 11)
- Diane Sasson (Box 11)
- Pat Round 2 (Box 11)
- WIN Major Donors (Box 11)
- WIN Back Pgs (Box 11)
- Unlabeled (Box 11)
- Kacky's Party (Box 11)
- Kacky's RSVP'S (Box 11)
- Lists (Box 11)
- Research Grants (Box 11)
- Kacky's Party (Box 11)